Contact

adityamailbox0@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ adityamailbox0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Django

Machine Learning

Python (Programming Language)

Languages

English (Elementary)

Certifications

NPTEL- ALGORITHM DESIGN AND ANALYSIS

NPTEL- DATA STRUCTURE

NPTEL - Machine Learning

Publications

Research paper in Machine Learning for disease prediction

aditya raj

Software Developer Internship at QLS Academy Pvt. Ltd.

Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh, India

Summary

Experienced Web Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in PostgreSQL, C ++, Django, ML, and CSS. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Computer Science from Lakshmi Narain College of Technology, Bhopal. I already have created alot of websites while working as a freelancer and so I manage everything from SEO to deployment.

Experience

QLS Academy Pvt. Ltd. Software Developer Internship February 2019 - Present

Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh, India

LNCT Group of Colleges Web Designer and Developer January 2017 - Present Bhopal

Education

Lakshmi Narain College of Technology, Kalchuri Nagar, Raisen Road, Post Klua, Bhopal-462021

· (2016 - 2020)

Lakshmi Narain College of Technology, Kalchuri Nagar, Raisen Road, Post Klua, Bhopal-462021

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)

Jawahar Vidya Mandir - Shyamali Intermediate, Computer Science · (2013 - 2015)